http://www.chattanooga.gov/it/web-policies/64-it/1444-website-privacy-policy

RT @AndyBerke: We’ve all had to make adjustments during the pandemic and that includes the way some of us work and how our children are lea…
View Our Facebook Page!
Contact
GovernmentBoards & CommissionsMayor's OfficeCity CouncilCity JudgesRegional GovernmentState GovernmentUnited States GovernmentTennessee Open RecordsBusinessConstructionBids and SolicitationsBusiness LicensesPay Property TaxChamber of CommerceEnterprise CenterGIS MapsEmploymentHuman ResourcesJob OpeningsInternal OpeningsJob DescriptionsJob Interest CardArts ArtsBuildPublic Art ChattanoogaRecreationBike ChattanoogaPublic Golf CoursesOutdoor ChattanoogaZooTourismParksResidentsBike ChattanoogaCARTAChattanooga AirportPublic LibraryNew ResidentsUnited WayAboutAbout ChattanoogaChattanooga in 3 MinutesChattanooga Sister CitiesGIS MapsHistory of MayorsWeb PoliciesPrivacy PolicyCalendarDepartmentsCity CouncilCity CourtEconomic & Community DevelopmentFinance & AdministrationFire DepartmentHuman ResourcesInformation TechnologyInternal AuditMayor's OfficeMulticultural AffairsOffice of the City AttorneyPolice DepartmentPublic LibraryPublic WorksPurchasingTransportationYouth & Family Development
Information Technology
Search
Search This Department Only
Search ResultsOpen Data PortalChattaDataConfidentiality AgreementWeb PoliciesTechnology Strategic Plan FY 15-18NoogaNet
Website Privacy Policy
The website for the City of Chattanooga ("City"), chattanooga.gov, is designed to encourage user participation in City government, to deliver electronic services to the public, and to help create a better Chattanooga for all. Toward that end, the City recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of this website's users.
Personal/confidential information
The City does not use its website to collect personal information for any purpose other than to respond to a user's request or input or to complete an online transaction, as more fully described below. The City does not collect information for commercial marketing from this site and will not send you unsolicited email for any commercial offers or advertisements at any time.
The City of Chattanooga does not create individual profiles with the information provided by users of this site, nor does it give such personal information to third parties or private organizations.
Any information collected by chattanooga.gov from children ages thirteen (13) and under is subject to the same guidelines of the City's general privacy policy.
Collection of limited information
The only information that the City automatically collects and stores about your visit to our website is the following:
The Fully Qualified Domain Name ("Domain Name") of your Internet Service Provider ("ISP") and/or your computer, if your computer has a Domain Name specifically assigned to it;
Your IP Address (the number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web) from which you access our website;
Your Browser Type (for example, Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, Mozilla Firefox, Opera);
Your Operating System you use to access our site (for example, Windows XP, Windows 2000, Macintosh OS, Linux);
The Date and Time you accessed our site;
The Pages you visited; and
The Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") of the page from which you started (for example, google.com) that linked you to our website, if you did not access our page by typing in our URL.
We do not use the information that is collected for marketing or commercial purposes nor do we distribute it in any way.
Our policy on "cookies"
A cookie is a small data file that certain websites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a session ID that the site uses to track the pages you have visited. A cookie cannot read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information that you supply.
Some parts of the City's website use cookies to track user sessions. We do this to determine if an individual has left the site and needs to log in again. The passive cookies used on this site do not remember you each time you visit the site.
If you prefer not to receive cookies while browsing our website, you can set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies and refuse the cookie when your browser alerts you to its presence. You also can refuse all cookies by turning them off in your browser, although you may not be able to take full advantage of this website if you do so. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use or navigate through many parts of our website. However, cookies must be accepted to access certain web pages that require a login and password.
Notwithstanding the above provisions of this section, information submitted to the City of Chattanooga's website may be subject to disclosure to a third party as provided by law.
Hosting of some content by outside parties
Some content on portions of this website resides on servers run by non-chattanooga.gov parties. The non-chattanooga.gov parties have direct control of what information is automatically gathered, whether cookies are used, and how voluntarily provided information is used, and thus we cannot represent that they abide by this privacy policy. Those City departments and applications that are currently hosted by outside parties are as follows:
FOIAView
Cityworks
Google
Brazos
FIS
Security
Unless a particular page on this website indicates that encryption technology is being used, the user should not assume that information uploaded through that Web page to the City of Chattanooga's Web server will be treated as confidential. If a user submits information to the server through a page containing visible indicators of active encryption technology, the City will take all reasonable precautions to safeguard the confidentiality of such information to the extent permitted by law. Nevertheless, the City shall not be liable for any injury caused by the disclosure of that information, whether caused by security breach, accident, inadvertence, or any other act resulting in disclosure.
×
Online Services
Finance
Pay Property Taxes Online
Lookup Property Tax
Pay Sewer Fee
City Council
District Lookup
government. To reach our Technical Assistance Center, please
call 423.643.6301.
Loading...
